Meaning of the seven columns for Yoon's data:

1) natural (1) vs. synthetic (2)
2) A frame
3) B frame
4) Size, I'm not exactly sure what this refers to, but I believe there were size differences among stimuli, possibly across different experiments.
5) Ignored in Olivier's code
6) What the X frame actually matches (e.g., 1 means it matches A, 2 means it matches B)
7) What the participant reported the X frame matches
